export const quizData = {
    formula1: [
      {
        question: "Who won the F1 World Championship in 2017?",
        options: ["Lewis Hamilton", "Max Verstappen", "Sebastian Vettel", "Charles Leclerc"],
        answer: "Lewis Hamilton",
      },
      {
        question: "Which team holds the record for most Constructors' Championships?",
        options: ["Ferrari", "Mercedes", "McLaren", "Red Bull Racing"],
        answer: "Ferrari",
      },
      {
        question: "Which driver has most wins in F1 History?",
        options: ["Lewis Hamilton", "Ayrton Senna", "Schumacher", "Lauda"],
        answer: "Lewis Hamilton",
      },
      {
        question: "Which driver has Most wins in a season?",
        options: ["Lewis Hamilton", "Ayrton Senna", "Schumacher", "Max Verstappen"],
        answer: "Max Verstappen",
      },
      {
        question: "which driver has Most races without a win?",
        options: ["Nico Hulkenberg", "Andrea de Cesaris", "Yuki Tsunoda", "Magnussen"],
        answer: "Nico Hulkenberg",
      },
      {
        question: "Driver With Most Pole Positions?",
        options: ["Senna", "Schumacher", "Lewis Hamilton", "Max Verstappen"],
        answer: "Lewis Hamilton",
      },
      {
        question: "Driver With Most consecutive pole positions at the same Grand Prix?",
        options: ["Senna", "Schumacher", "Lewis Hamilton", "Max Verstappen"],
        answer: "Senna",
      },
      
    ],
    ucl: [
      {
        question: "Which team has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
        options: ["Real Madrid", "Barcelona", "Bayern Munich", "Liverpool"],
        answer: "Real Madrid",
      },
      {
        question: "Who was the top scorer in the 2019-2020 UCL season?",
        options: ["Robert Lewandowski", "Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Erling Haaland"],
        answer: "Robert Lewandowski",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Player Has Most Carrer wins on UCL ?",
        options: ["Robert Lewandowski", "Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Iker Casilas"],
        answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Player is Top Scorer of UCL?",
        options: ["Robert Lewandowski", "Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Benzema"],
        answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      },
      {
        question: "Who is Oldest Player which Scored a Goal in UCL",
        options: ["Benzema", "Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Pepe"],
        answer: "Pepe",
      },
      
    ],
    lemans: [
      {
        question: "Which manufacturer has the most Le Mans wins?",
        options: ["Porsche", "Toyota", "Audi", "Ford"],
        answer: "Porsche",
      },
      {
        question: "How long does the Le Mans race last?",
        options: ["12 hours", "24 hours", "36 hours", "48 hours"],
        answer: "24 hours",
      },
      {
        question: "which nation have most Le Mans Win?",
        options: ["Germany", "France", "Italy", "Great-Britan"],
        answer: "Germany",
      },
      {
        question: "Manufacturer With Most 1-2 Finishes?",
        options: ["Porsche", "Ferrari", "Audi", "BMW"],
        answer: "Porsche",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Manufacturer Have Most participations without winning?",
        options: ["BMW", "Toyota", "Bentley", "Chevrolet"],
        answer: "Chevrolet",
      },
      
    ],
    motogp: [
      {
        question: "Who won the MotoGP World Championship in 2020?",
        options: ["Joan Mir", "Marc Marquez", "Valentino Rossi", "Fabio Quartararo"],
        answer: "Joan Mir",
      },
      {
        question: "Which country hosts the Mugello circuit?",
        options: ["Italy", "Spain", "France", "Portugal"],
        answer: "Italy",
      },
      {
        question: "Which country hosts the MONZA circuit?",
        options: ["Italy", "Spain", "France", "Portugal"],
        answer: "Italy",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Rider has most entries?",
        options: ["Valentino ROSSI", "Jorge Lorenzo", "Joan Mir", "Andrea Dovizioso"],
        answer: "Valentino ROSSI",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Rider has most Pole position?",
        options: ["Valentino ROSSI", "Freddie Spencer", "Marc Marquez", "Max Biaggi"],
        answer: "Marc Marquez",
      },
      {
        question: "Driver With most Points?",
        options: ["Valentino ROSSI", "Dani Pedrosa", "Marc Marquez", "Jorje Lorenzo"],
        answer: "Valentino ROSSI",
      },
      
    ],
  };
  